# PRINCY DUBEY

Dedicated Financial Analyst with 7 years of strong experience in the order-to-cash process and contract set-up. I have a comprehensive understanding of billing operations and a track record of delivering accurate and efficient billing services. Great at multitasking. Looking to succeed in a stimulating and challenging environment to build the success of the organization while experiencing advancement opportunities.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### OTC OPERATIONS ANALYST

Accenture | Pune

September 2024 - Present.

#### FINANCIAL ANALYST

FIS Global Solutions | Pune

February 2021 - August 2024

- Streamlined the process of managing new deals and renewals from the Bitsy portal by implementing a standardized setup in SAP to enhance overall operational efficiency for the billing team.
- Reviewing and finalizing invoices for global customers with 20M+ in revenue for an average of 70+ clients.
- Prioritizing high-dollar invoices at the beginning of the month to ensure timely revenue recognition.
- Resolving billing discrepancies and inquiries within established turnaround times.
- Prepare various reports, such as the Bitsy Report, Billing Block Report, Expiration, Unbilled Report, Sales Order, and Quotations, to ensure billing transparency.
- Collaborating with cross-functional teams, including sales and customer service, to streamline processes and enhance client satisfaction
- Ensure APE has been applied correctly and send APE letters to the clients. Generating invoices for license and support as per the overage billing based on the AUM.
- Validate the auto-renewal term of the contract to extend the billing term and keep track of the contract. So, the errors in SAP should be corrected to adjust the end date of billing accordingly.
- Raise a dispute with appropriate comments along with all the approvals and attachments in case of NFI.
- Ensure a smooth billing close by clearing all billing lines and finalizing them so that there are no unbilled lines.
- Provided comprehensive cross-training to new joiners, ensuring seamless product knowledge transfer and a smooth transition.
- Coordinate with sales and project manager for renewal and extension of contract for their pricing, terms, and user accounts.
- Working on various reports of SAP to help resolve the billing queries in a timely manner.
- Termination of services and products, as per the termination clause in the contract and provided by the client, to discontinue the services.
- Performing the Credit Memo against the invoice which are disputed in Get paid.
- Reviewing and preparing monthly recurring files billing and variance report for accurate billing.

### Finance Administrator

Fujitsu Consulting India Pvt Ltd | Pune, India December 2017 - February 2021

## **AR Billing**

- Hardware and software maintenance service billing. Setting up new customer accounts in the ERP Oracle according to the signed Master Agreement.
- Billing/invoicing of new maintenance services, as per customer request.
- Termination of maintenance services, preparing of credit calculation on the request received from customer with all terms and conditions applied as per master agreement.
- Performing Service Billing either through manual procedure or Auto-load, for activities such as Install, T&M,
  Professional Services, Project Management, Help Desk request, Service Desk request, Supply point, and Freight Charges, etc.
- Submitted invoices on various customer portals, such as SAP Ariba, I payable portal, Transcript portal, and Coupa Portal.
- Preparing daily AR revenue report for the team.

## General Ledger Accounting

- To ensure all the task with the minimum rejections according to SLAs of the timeliness and accuracy of each process and the future of action adhere to the client.
- Reconciliation of Depreciation account maintains fixed asset clearing account and reconcile it.
- Posting the reclass entries.
- Preparation of Bank reconciliation statement and resolved external auditor's queries.
- Preparing the journal entries which includes accrual, amortization & deferred entries.
- Preparing Monthly addition, retirement & cost adjustment report report.
- Asset creation.

# **ACHIEVEMETS**

- Won Above & Beyond Award in Q2 -2023 for outstanding performance and embracing FIS Values.
- Won Kudos for demonstrating exemplary efforts in understanding & take over Ambit License & Support billing.
- Recognized with Spot Award for managing an unprecedented volume of deals in Q2 2023, maintaining zero escalations and contributing to a seamless customer experience that improved retention rates across the board at Fujitsu.

## **EDUCATION**

#### MASTER OF BUSINESS ADMINISTATION (FINANCE)

Bharati Vidyapeeth Deemed

University, Pune (2015-2017).

# **SKILLS & TOOLS**

- Account Receivable
- Dispute Management
- Revenue Recognition
- Customer Service
- SAP
- MS-Excel

- Troubleshooter
- Effective Communicator
- Meticulous
- Proactive
- Power BI

# PERSONAL DETAILS

- Date of Birth- 28th January 1992
- Gender- Female
- Languages- English, Hindi, Marathi.
- LinkedIn Profile- www.linkedin.com/in/princydubey28